<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Asset on Edge Engineering</title>
    <link>//localhost:39863/asset/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Asset on Edge Engineering</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:39863/asset/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Preventative Maintenance</title>
      <link>//localhost:39863/asset/pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:39863/asset/pm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At Edge Engineering, we understand that maintaining your machinery in top condition is essential to avoid costly downtime and ensure smooth operation. That is why we offer comprehensive preventative maintenance solutions, tailored to keep your equipment running efficiently and reliably.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each machine registered in our maintenance system is fitted with a QR code tag, enabling users to instantly submit work requests directly to our scheduling system. This feature also allows the submission of critical information, including photos, required parts, and detailed notes, streamlining the process. Our comprehensive records include essential details such as machine manuals, the history of previous work orders, parts inventories, and key metrics like planned and unplanned downtime. We are committed to responding to work requests within one hour, striving to minimise downtime and ensure seamless operations for our clients.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Inspection &amp; Servicing</title>
      <link>//localhost:39863/asset/inspect-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:39863/asset/inspect-service/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our advanced maintenance programme provides thorough inspections and systematic servicing on a 6-month, 12-month, or as-needed basis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each machine is inspected and serviced methodically, with a comprehensive report provided for every unit. We also collect critical machine data, including oil types, filters, and replacement parts, to enable efficient servicing and minimise machine downtime.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Monitoring</title>
      <link>//localhost:39863/asset/remote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:39863/asset/remote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We install advanced maintenance sensors that connect directly to the cloud, enabling seamless remote monitoring of vital machine metrics such as oil levels, runtime, current, and other critical parameters. The system is fully self-sufficient, ensuring consistent operation without external dependencies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Clients can access real-time data through an intuitive interface, keeping them informed at all times. This capability empowers proactive maintenance, allowing timely responses to potential issues before they escalate into costly breakdowns, ultimately enhancing machine uptime and operational efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operator Application</title>
      <link>//localhost:39863/asset/operator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:39863/asset/operator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The EDGE operator app, mounted on a tablet attached directly to the machine, acts as a centralised hub for efficient maintenance management. It features a structured daily or weekly checklist with clear, step-by-step instructions, guiding operators through critical routine tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By ensuring these checks are consistently performed, the app promotes regular machine upkeep and significantly reduces the risk of maintenance oversights.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, it seamlessly integrates with remote sensor data, providing real-time alerts for potential monitoring alarms. This synergy of routine management and real-time diagnostics enhances machine reliability and supports proactive maintenance strategies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
