<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Asset Management on Edge Engineering</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/asset-managment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Asset Management on Edge Engineering</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/asset-managment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Remote Monitoring</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/asset-managment/remote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/asset-managment/remote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We install advanced maintenance sensors that connect directly to the cloud, enabling seamless remote monitoring of vital machine metrics such as oil levels, runtime, current, and other critical parameters. The system is fully self-sufficient, ensuring consistent operation without external dependencies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Clients can access real-time data through an intuitive interface, keeping them informed at all times. This capability empowers proactive maintenance, allowing timely responses to potential issues before they escalate into costly breakdowns, ultimately enhancing machine uptime and operational efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preventative Maintenance</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/asset-managment/pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/asset-managment/pm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At Edge Engineering, we understand that maintaining your machinery in top condition is essential to avoid costly downtime and ensure smooth operation. That is why we offer comprehensive preventative maintenance solutions, tailored to keep your equipment running efficiently and reliably.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inpsecting and Servicing</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/asset-managment/inspect-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/asset-managment/inspect-service/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our advanced maintenance programme includes thorough inspections, systematic servicing, and the latest in remote monitoring technology.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By implementing sensors on your machinery, we collect critical data—such as oil levels, runtime, and other performance metrics—allowing us to monitor equipment &amp;ldquo;health&amp;rdquo; in real time and address potential issues before they escalate.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Monitoring</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/asset-managment/operator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/asset-managment/operator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The EDGE operator app, mounted on a tablet attached directly to the machine, acts as a centralised hub for efficient maintenance management. It features a structured daily or weekly checklist with clear, step-by-step instructions, guiding operators through critical routine tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By ensuring these checks are consistently performed, the app promotes regular machine upkeep and significantly reduces the risk of maintenance oversights.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, it seamlessly integrates with remote sensor data, providing real-time alerts for potential monitoring alarms. This synergy of routine management and real-time diagnostics enhances machine reliability and supports proactive maintenance strategies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
