<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Edge Engineering</title>
    <link>//localhost:42527/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Edge Engineering</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:42527/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>APEC</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/sales/apec/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/sales/apec/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With decades of expertise in advanced manufacturing, Asia Pacific Elite Corp. (APEC) is a leader in producing 5-axis large-scale machining centers designed for the aerospace and die &amp;amp; mold industries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Renowned for their precision, innovation, and comprehensive solutions, APEC’s machines meet the most demanding requirements. As the official distributor and servicing agent for APEC, we provide their cutting-edge machinery along with expert support to ensure exceptional performance and customer satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Relocation &amp; Commissioning</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/services/relocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/services/relocation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Edge Engineering provides expert machine transport, installation, and commissioning, ensuring a seamless and efficient transition for new or relocated equipment. Whether moving a single machine or an entire production line, every detail is managed with precision and care to minimise downtime and disruption.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preventative Maintenance</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/asset/pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/asset/pm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At Edge Engineering, we understand that maintaining your machinery in top condition is essential to avoid costly downtime and ensure smooth operation. That is why we offer comprehensive preventative maintenance solutions, tailored to keep your equipment running efficiently and reliably.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each machine registered in our maintenance system is fitted with a QR code tag, enabling users to instantly submit work requests directly to our scheduling system. This feature also allows the submission of critical information, including photos, required parts, and detailed notes, streamlining the process. Our comprehensive records include essential details such as machine manuals, the history of previous work orders, parts inventories, and key metrics like planned and unplanned downtime. We are committed to responding to work requests within one hour, striving to minimise downtime and ensure seamless operations for our clients.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakdown Repairs</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/services/breakdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/services/breakdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Edge Engineering understands that machinery downtime is costly, which is why we respond quickly and proactively to breakdowns. Our skilled team provides precise, efficient on-site repairs, equipped with the tools and expertise to minimise disruption. For more complex issues, our Kenwick workshop offers thorough overhauls and rebuilds, backed by a strong supplier network to ensure fast part sourcing. Whether your machine tool needs minor fixes or a major rebuild, we are ready to restore full operation promptly and reliably.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Inspection &amp; Servicing</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/asset/inspect-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/asset/inspect-service/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our advanced maintenance programme provides thorough inspections and systematic servicing on a 6-month, 12-month, or as-needed basis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each machine is inspected and serviced methodically, with a comprehensive report provided for every unit. We also collect critical machine data, including oil types, filters, and replacement parts, to enable efficient servicing and minimise machine downtime.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/sales/radar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/sales/radar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Radar Industrial Co., Ltd., established in 2007 with over 50 years of expertise, specialises in high-precision CNC vertical lathes for heavy cutting processes. Their machines feature advanced design, exceptional stability, and ease of operation, delivering superior performance and efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With a strong focus on quality, innovation, and customer satisfaction, Radar offers reliable &amp;ldquo;before and after&amp;rdquo; service, competitive pricing, and fast delivery. As the official distributor and servicing agent, we proudly provide Radar’s machinery alongside expert support to ensure optimal performance for every customer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EUMACH</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/sales/eumach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/sales/eumach/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Edge Engineering specialises in precision rebuilds and retrofits, transforming worn or outdated machinery into high-performing, reliable assets. Our rebuild services go beyond simple repairs, addressing all critical components to restore your equipment to peak condition. This includes reconditioning mechanical systems, restoring precision, and ensuring all safety and performance standards are met.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Retrofits provide a cost-effective way to enhance the capabilities of existing equipment without the need for a full replacement. By upgrading control systems, integrating advanced technology, or improving automation, we bring your machinery up to date, increasing efficiency, accuracy, and productivity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Team</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/about-us/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/about-us/team/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:42527/images/about-us/workshop1_crop.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The Edge Team&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edge Engineering takes pride in employing highly skilled and qualified staff who excel in high-pressure environments while maintaining a calm and professional approach. We are privileged to have team members who not only elevate our technical expertise but also embody our family-oriented business values.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With decades of combined experience, our team brings a wide range of specialised skills, including:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Extensive mechanical expertise in rebuilds and repairs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Spindle rebuilding&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Precision hand scraping, blueing, and high-accuracy craftsmanship&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mechanical design and drafting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hydraulic and pneumatic system design and installation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Machine tool alignment&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Electronics expertise with leading CNC brands such as Siemens, Fagor, Heidenhain, and Fanuc controllers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Transport, packaging, and logistics of machine tools&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our team’s diverse capabilities ensure we deliver exceptional service across all areas of machine tool maintenance and engineering.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebuilds - Restoring Machinery</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/services/rebuilds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/services/rebuilds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Edge Engineering specialises in precision rebuilds and retrofits, transforming worn or outdated machinery into high-performing, reliable assets. Our rebuild services go beyond simple repairs, addressing all critical components to restore your equipment to peak condition. This includes reconditioning mechanical systems, restoring precision, and ensuring all safety and performance standards are met.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Retrofits provide a cost-effective way to enhance the capabilities of existing equipment without the need for a full replacement. By upgrading control systems, integrating advanced technology, or improving automation, we bring your machinery up to date, increasing efficiency, accuracy, and productivity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Monitoring</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/asset/remote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/asset/remote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We install advanced maintenance sensors that connect directly to the cloud, enabling seamless remote monitoring of vital machine metrics such as oil levels, runtime, current, and other critical parameters. The system is fully self-sufficient, ensuring consistent operation without external dependencies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Clients can access real-time data through an intuitive interface, keeping them informed at all times. This capability empowers proactive maintenance, allowing timely responses to potential issues before they escalate into costly breakdowns, ultimately enhancing machine uptime and operational efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operator Application</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/asset/operator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/asset/operator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The EDGE operator app, mounted on a tablet attached directly to the machine, acts as a centralised hub for efficient maintenance management. It features a structured daily or weekly checklist with clear, step-by-step instructions, guiding operators through critical routine tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By ensuring these checks are consistently performed, the app promotes regular machine upkeep and significantly reduces the risk of maintenance oversights.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, it seamlessly integrates with remote sensor data, providing real-time alerts for potential monitoring alarms. This synergy of routine management and real-time diagnostics enhances machine reliability and supports proactive maintenance strategies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrofits - Advancing Machinery</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/services/retrofits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/services/retrofits/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Edge Engineering specialises in precision rebuilds and retrofits, transforming worn or outdated machinery into high-performing, reliable assets. Our rebuild services go beyond simple repairs, addressing all critical components to restore your equipment to peak condition. This includes reconditioning mechanical systems, restoring precision, and ensuring all safety and performance standards are met.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Retrofits provide a cost-effective way to enhance the capabilities of existing equipment without the need for a full replacement. By upgrading control systems, integrating advanced technology, or improving automation, we bring your machinery up to date, increasing efficiency, accuracy, and productivity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUN FIRM MACHINERY</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/sales/sunfirm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/sales/sunfirm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With 60 years of expertise in lathe manufacturing, Sun Firm Machinery is a trusted name in producing horizontal heavy-duty giant CNC lathes and precision lathes tailored to customer requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Known for their exceptional craftsmanship and reliability, Sun Firm&amp;rsquo;s machines are ideal for demanding applications. As the official distributor and servicing agent for Sun Firm, we deliver their high-quality machinery along with expert support to ensure optimal performance and customer satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNECO RAIL</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/sales/uneco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/sales/uneco/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With over 40 years of expertise, Uneco Rail is the leading manufacturer of railroad vehicle wheel processing and inspection facilities in their home country. They provide a comprehensive range of equipment, including CNC brake disc wheel lathes, CNC wheel set measuring systems, and various railway maintenance tools. Edge Engineering is proud to represent Uneco Rail in Australia as they expand into the environmental industry, serving global markets with innovative and reliable solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Workshop</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/about-us/workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/about-us/workshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:42527/images/about-us/lift4_crop1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Workshop&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our Kenwick workshop is a state-of-the-art facility designed to handle a wide range of machine repairs, rebuilds, and servicing needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Spanning 1,000 sqm with a 40-tonne overhead crane capacity, it features an additional 1,000 sqm under-crane repair area with a 25-tonne crane and a 1,300 sqm outdoor hardstand area.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The workshop is fully equipped with advanced machinery for repairs and modifications, supported by an integrated office space for 10+ staff. Combining cutting-edge tools with the expertise of our skilled team, the Kenwick workshop ensures high-quality results for every project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;contact-us&#34;&gt;Contact Us&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our offices and workshop are conveniently located, providing easy access for all your machine servicing and engineering needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Feel free to visit us or get in touch to learn more about our services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edge Engineering&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9 Freight Road, Kenwick, WA6107, Australia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Telephone:&lt;/strong&gt; 0438 994 774&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;E-mail:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jim@edgeeng.com.au&#34;&gt;jim@edgeeng.com.au&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;block&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;google-map&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;iframe width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;600px&#34; frameBorder=&#34;0&#34; src=&#34;https://umap.openstreetmap.fr/en/map/untitled-map_1119662?scaleControl=true&amp;miniMap=true&amp;scrollWheelZoom=true&amp;zoomControl=true&amp;allowEdit=false&amp;moreControl=false&amp;searchControl=true&amp;tilelayersControl=null&amp;embedControl=false&amp;datalayersControl=null&amp;onLoadPanel=none&amp;captionBar=false&amp;fullscreenControl=null#15/-32.009562/115.980585&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn More</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/landing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/landing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;who-we-are&#34;&gt;Who We Are&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:42527/images/pages/landing_crop.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The Edge Team&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edge Engineering recognises that machinery downtime is costly, which is why we respond quickly and proactively to breakdowns. Our experienced team provides efficient on-site repairs with precision, using the tools and expertise needed to minimise operational disruption. For more complex issues, our Kenwick workshop delivers complete overhauls, supported by strong supplier partnerships to ensure the rapid sourcing of critical parts. Whether your machine tool requires minor repairs or significant restoration, we are committed to restoring full functionality promptly and reliably.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/about-us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-us&#34;&gt;About Us&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Founded with the vision of providing unmatched customer service and support to Australia’s manufacturing industry, Edge Engineering has grown to become a trusted name. Our team members bring diverse experience and skills, from hands-on service and repair to sales and application expertise. Our commitment to old-fashioned values like honesty, reliability, and a personal approach defines our success. Every day, we strive to exceed customer expectations and adapt to the evolving needs of the manufacturing industry. Our goal is to provide unparalleled quality and service, building lasting partnerships with our clients for a successful future together.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allgo</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/partners/allgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/partners/allgo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asset</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/asset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/asset/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-asset-management-services&#34;&gt;Our Asset Management Services&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edge Engineering ensures efficient, reliable machinery operation with tailored maintenance solutions. Using advanced sensors, QR-tagged machines, and the EDGE operator app, we streamline inspections, servicing, and real-time monitoring to address issues proactively, minimize downtime, and optimize performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chess Engineering</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/partners/chessengineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/partners/chessengineering/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emerson</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/partners/emerson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/partners/emerson/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mincon</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/partners/mincon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/partners/mincon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Your privacy is important to us. It is Edge Engineering&amp;rsquo;s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.edgeeng.com.au/&#34;&gt;https://www.edgeeng.com.au/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RCR Engineering</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/partners/rcrengineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/partners/rcrengineering/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sales</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/sales/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;sales&#34;&gt;Sales&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edge Engineering provides high-quality, tested machinery at affordable prices, backed by a proven track record in the Perth market. As the official distributor for leading Taiwanese and Korean manufacturers, we offer a comprehensive range of CNC lathes, vertical turning lathes, and 5-axis machining centres, including vertical, universal bed-type, and double-column models.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our service goes beyond sales. Edge Engineering can organise transport, installation, and commissioning, ensuring a seamless setup for your new machinery. Throughout the machine’s lifetime, you benefit from guaranteed service and priority support. Thanks to our close relationships with manufacturers, we ensure the fastest possible sourcing of parts, minimising downtime.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schlumberger</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/partners/schlumberger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/partners/schlumberger/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/services/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-machinery-services&#34;&gt;Our Machinery Services&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Founded on decades of combined experience, Edge Engineering ensures efficient machinery support with fast breakdown repairs, precision rebuilds, and advanced retrofits to enhance performance. They also offer seamless machine relocation and commissioning, minimising downtime and maximising operational reliability.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UWA</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/partners/uwa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/partners/uwa/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veem Group</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/partners/veem-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/partners/veem-group/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Westrac</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/partners/westrac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/partners/westrac/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
