<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sales on Edge Engineering</title>
    <link>//localhost:42527/sales/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sales on Edge Engineering</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:42527/sales/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>APEC</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/sales/apec/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/sales/apec/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With decades of expertise in advanced manufacturing, Asia Pacific Elite Corp. (APEC) is a leader in producing 5-axis large-scale machining centers designed for the aerospace and die &amp;amp; mold industries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Renowned for their precision, innovation, and comprehensive solutions, APEC’s machines meet the most demanding requirements. As the official distributor and servicing agent for APEC, we provide their cutting-edge machinery along with expert support to ensure exceptional performance and customer satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/sales/radar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/sales/radar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Radar Industrial Co., Ltd., established in 2007 with over 50 years of expertise, specialises in high-precision CNC vertical lathes for heavy cutting processes. Their machines feature advanced design, exceptional stability, and ease of operation, delivering superior performance and efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With a strong focus on quality, innovation, and customer satisfaction, Radar offers reliable &amp;ldquo;before and after&amp;rdquo; service, competitive pricing, and fast delivery. As the official distributor and servicing agent, we proudly provide Radar’s machinery alongside expert support to ensure optimal performance for every customer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EUMACH</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/sales/eumach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/sales/eumach/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Edge Engineering specialises in precision rebuilds and retrofits, transforming worn or outdated machinery into high-performing, reliable assets. Our rebuild services go beyond simple repairs, addressing all critical components to restore your equipment to peak condition. This includes reconditioning mechanical systems, restoring precision, and ensuring all safety and performance standards are met.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Retrofits provide a cost-effective way to enhance the capabilities of existing equipment without the need for a full replacement. By upgrading control systems, integrating advanced technology, or improving automation, we bring your machinery up to date, increasing efficiency, accuracy, and productivity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUN FIRM MACHINERY</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/sales/sunfirm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/sales/sunfirm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With 60 years of expertise in lathe manufacturing, Sun Firm Machinery is a trusted name in producing horizontal heavy-duty giant CNC lathes and precision lathes tailored to customer requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Known for their exceptional craftsmanship and reliability, Sun Firm&amp;rsquo;s machines are ideal for demanding applications. As the official distributor and servicing agent for Sun Firm, we deliver their high-quality machinery along with expert support to ensure optimal performance and customer satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNECO RAIL</title>
      <link>//localhost:42527/sales/uneco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:42527/sales/uneco/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With over 40 years of expertise, Uneco Rail is the leading manufacturer of railroad vehicle wheel processing and inspection facilities in their home country. They provide a comprehensive range of equipment, including CNC brake disc wheel lathes, CNC wheel set measuring systems, and various railway maintenance tools. Edge Engineering is proud to represent Uneco Rail in Australia as they expand into the environmental industry, serving global markets with innovative and reliable solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
