<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About Us on Edge Engineering</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/personnel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About Us on Edge Engineering</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/personnel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jim Kendrick - Director</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/personnel/jim-kendrick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/personnel/jim-kendrick/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/images/personnel/jim-kendrick.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Jim Kendrick&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jim is a Fitter/Machinist specializing as a machine tool fitter for over 15 years experience in the maintenance and serving industry. Having trained as an apprentice at Hofmann Engineering he has had a broad range of exposure to different machine tools and challenging scenarios. Stepping out to start Edge Engineering in 2014 after sensing the opportunity to fill a void in the maintenance market he has witness the business grow from strength to strength. Jim possesses the following skills:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Martin Gonser - Workshop Manager</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/personnel/martin-gonser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/personnel/martin-gonser/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/images/personnel/martin-gonser.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Martin Gonser&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Martin is a Fitter/Machinist joining Edge Engineering over three years ago and has worked as a machine tool fitter for over 15 years after also training and working at Hofmann Engineering. Martin directly supervises the fitters employed by Edge Engineering ensuring all work is carried out to his lofty high standards. Martin possess the following skills:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Extensive mechanical knowledge, rebuild and repair experience&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Spindle Rebuilds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hand scraping, blueing and high accuracy hand skills&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hydraulic and Pneumatic design and installation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Machine tool alignment&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Exposure to Siemens, Fagor, Heidenhein and Fanuc controllers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Transport, packaging, and logistics of machine tools&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dwayne Conti - Mechanical Fitter</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/personnel/dwayne-conti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/personnel/dwayne-conti/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/images/personnel/dwayne-conti.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Dwayne Conti&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dwayne joined Edge Engineering in 2018 and is a Fitter/ Machinist trained at Hofmann Engineering with high exposure to final drive and gearbox fitting. Dwayne has transitioned into the machine tool servicing role seamlessly showing great competence in attention to detail and customer relations. Dwayne possesses the following skills:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sound mechanical aptitude and rebuild skills of gearboxes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hydraulic experience&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Servicing and maintenance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Project management skills&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve Hair - Mechanical Fitter</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/personnel/steve-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/personnel/steve-hair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/images/personnel/steve-hair.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Steve Hair&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Steve joined Edge Engineering early 2019 coming from RCR mining as their main maintenance fitter. Steve has over 30 years’ experience as a fitter/machinist having served his apprenticeship at Warman Pumps in NSW. Steve possess excellent fault finding and diagnostic skill and is Edge Engineering’s main machinist / tool maker. Steve possesses the following skills:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sound mechanical aptitude and rebuild skills&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hydraulic experience&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Servicing and maintenance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Extensive tool making skills&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Highly competent machinist&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scott Matherson - Junior Mechanical Fitter</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/personnel/scott-matherson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/personnel/scott-matherson/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/images/personnel/scott-matherson.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Scott Matherson&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scott had worked for Edge Engineering for the past three years after a long time out of the engineering industry. Scott is a Geologist that has owned and run his business before stepping away and changing industries. Scott has over 30 years’ experience rebuilding, servicing, and restoring motorcycles and vintage cars. Scott works closely with the mechanical fitters at Edge Engineering and has proven to be an asset to the business. Scott possesses the following skills:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Henning Mohr - Amateur Kite Surfer</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/personnel/henning-mohr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/personnel/henning-mohr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/images/personnel/henning-mohr.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Henning Mohr&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Henning joined Edge Engineering in 2022 after a break in the sea breeze in Cottesloe left him with little to do. Against all his instincts, he found his way from the Western suburbs to Kenwick and has been working for Edge Engineering ever since. Henning possesses the following skills:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Average kite surfer&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&amp;hellip;?!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
